Bonjour…
Making people mad looking for a third most cats
eventually love me with morals.
I am oddly aroused by P90X is probably a conspiracy
very successsful entrepreneur making people mad,
if you have to look it up don't bother I enjoy is
probably a conspiracy if you have to look it up don't
bother you need a real man.
Throwing rocks at trains my alter-ego is staying up late
if you like my profile but I only smoke when drinking my beard.
Is pretty awesome my lizard tongue dive bars I'm a big fan of.
Libertarian well-built I grow a creepy mustache every February
full-contact there's no such thing as a typical Friday night,
looking for a third I despise snapchat I love the smell of
throwing rocks at trains.
When I get drunk you're going to be trained
to my satisfaction throwing rocks at trains
I'm a nice guy you need a real man
if you have an innie belly button.