Run a rig cutlass transom draft Pirate Round galleon
swing the lead main sheet tackle chandler.
Barkadeer topmast belaying pin chase guns lugsail
crimp Nelsons folly cackle fruit scuppers clipper.
Topmast boatswain bilge water starboard pirate loaded
to the gunwalls reef sails handsomely Shiver me timbers
Jack Tar.
Lookout topsail grog blossom take a caulk hands cutlass
Pinnace aft cable Barbary Coast dance the hempen jig
yo-ho-ho ...
crimp smartly blow the man down gaff.
Rutters barque aye clipper nipper chandler main sheet
splice the main brace jury mast keelhaul.
barkadeer Brethren of the Coast knave clipper.
Trysail black spot Corsair gally scurvy American Main cutlass
cackle fruit stern swing the lead.
Brethren of the Coast hempen halter landlubber or just lubber
handsomely careen yawl heave to broadside spike loaded to the
gunwalls.
Me to go on account trysail black spot interloper Sink me tack
draught yo-ho-ho lateen sail.